[
  {
    "question": "________ you like a cup of coffee?",
    "answer": "Would"
  },
  {
    "question": "Did You remember ____ (lock) the door?",
    "answer": "locking"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ (Who or whose) book is this?",
    "answer": "Whose"
  },
  {
    "question": "While I _______(wash) the dishes last night, I dropped a plate and broke it.",
    "answer": "was washing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Green ______(teach) at the University since 1989.",
    "answer": "has been teaching"
  },
  {
    "question": "A famous architect ___________(build) the bridge.",
    "answer": "built"
  },
  {
    "question": "This dictionary _______(publish) a week ago.",
    "answer": "was published"
  },
  {
    "question": "I ________(talk) to my dog when you came.",
    "answer": "had been talking"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now, many scientists from other countries_____(think) over the issues that affect leadership in technology.",
    "answer": "are thinking"
  },
  {
    "question": "They manage to make a difference in political life in spite of ______ (have)certain failures in this area.",
    "answer": "having"
  },
  {
    "question": "The judge _____ (gave|sentenced) him to ten years in prison.(выбрать и написать)",
    "answer": "sentenced"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you remember ________ some milk?",
    "answer": "to buy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Everyone wanted to go out ______ John.",
    "answer": "except"
  },
  {
    "question": "I did this painting all _____ my own.",
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am not really sure if I can do it but I'll______it a go.",
    "answer": "give"
  },
  {
    "question": "While we’re working on the project our boss _____________(sit) on a beach in Greece!",
    "answer": "will be sitting"
  },
  {
    "question": "There aren’t _____________ (много) places left on the course so you’d better apply soon.",
    "answer": "many"
  },
  {
    "question": "I know it’s not much of a present but I made it _____________ (сам).",
    "answer": "myself"
  },
  {
    "question": "The bookshop _____________ the end of the road is excellent.",
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "question": "This factory produces some of _____________ (good)cameras in the world.",
    "answer": "the best"
  },
  {
    "question": "She always complains that she has______ (мало)money.",
    "answer": "little"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow by the evening the room______ (paint).",
    "answer": "will have been painted"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you _________ (shut) the window now, it will be extremely hot inside.",
    "answer": "don’t shut"
  },
  {
    "question": "We would have lost all our money if the investor _________ (announce) himself a bankrupt.",
    "answer": "had announced"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes, I like this dress. I don't want _______ one.",
    "answer": "another"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anuar is the only friend _____ I would really confide something like this.",
    "answer": "in whom"
  },
  {
    "question": "The customer sevice advisor _____ I spoke was incredibly helpful and efficent.",
    "answer": "to whom"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think I ________ (hear) from her since we ________ (meet) in Chelyabinsk. (ответ писать через запятую)",
    "answer": "heaven't heard, met"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reason _____ I did it like that was to avoid paying delivery fees.",
    "answer": "why"
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ was my best friend who advised me not to accept the job offer.",
    "answer": "It"
  }
]
